<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Slides | R for Business Analytics</title><link>https://aem2850.toddgerarden.com/slides/</link><atom:link href="https://aem2850.toddgerarden.com/slides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Slides</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><item><title/><link>https://aem2850.toddgerarden.com/slides/data/survey-responses-midsemester/notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aem2850.toddgerarden.com/slides/data/survey-responses-midsemester/notes/</guid><description>&lt;p>AEM 2850 survey themes&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>What people want to cover in the second half of the semester
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Maybe if we could tie this into financial modelling, I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure how so I can&amp;rsquo;t give specifics, but maybe we could find a way to use R the same way as people as who work with R do. (As in work with R in a business field.)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Applying R to finance&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Want to see business applications&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How do analyze datasets in a business application&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A business application would be cool!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I would love to see more business application stuff!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>For example: stock returns, portfolio analysis&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Financial data&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More focus on how R is used in business applications&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I would definitely like to see more of how R is applied in business&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More theory / technique behind successful data visualization&lt;/li>
&lt;li>What are some examples of ways that R can be used more efficiently than Excel? Specifically interested re: a summer internship&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I hope that we learn about how to approach analyzing a dataset, including cleaning a dataset and ultimately visualizing the data. Although we learned many tools, I feel that we are practicing specific tools. I want to be able to be given a dataset and know how I could approach it as I would in the workplace.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Powerpoint?
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Maybe they mean making slide decks via Rmd?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More knitting examples to useful deliverables (e.g. excel sheets or docx)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Looping in R (while/for)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Business applications would be fun. I would love to explore applying our own concepts to R or creating our own code eventually.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I would like to learn a little about the Shiny package and how to use it.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Since I have already learned about many basic R and packages, so in the next half semester, I’d like to learn more about the data visualization part. The 3-D plot is one of the things that fascinates me most.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If possible, after we learn more complicated data visualization content later, maybe we can choose some real world examples instead of already processed tidy data for practice.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>It would be nice to learn about what to do when &amp;ldquo;troubleshooting.&amp;rdquo; (ie. how to use stuff like stackexchange/or how to determine what is wrong with your code/approach).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Also, learning how to do basic linear regression would be nice (scatterplot etc)!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“Using R for a personal project could be interesting, where each person finds a need or situation in their current life where R could be helpful (for me, I can think of one being tracking my golf stats this spring season).”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&amp;ldquo;It would be interesting to learn some examples about how R studio is actually used in a business setting. For example, a lesson on what kind of business jobs require a strong understanding of R studio and how it is applied on a daily basis.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“I think the course is well structured and the only issues come from people having different levels of previous experience with R, so for some the pace is rapid and for some it is not fast enough.”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I would like to learn more about using local R and more statistical methods that I could apply in other classes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“Data visualization and modeling. I also want more experience using business-related datasets and going through the process that a business analytics professional would do, since this course is geared to business analytics with R. I think this course can be distinguished from other data science courses by using a more business or economics lens. I would love using business datasets or even economics datasets that Dyson faculty may use in their research!”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Remove scaffolding to challenge students and help them learn (per their request!)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“I like the completion aspect of the assignments. It really allows me to genuinely try to solve the labs rather than vigorously stressing about getting it all right. It is a nice change of pace from other classes and puts more emphasis on learning which college should be about!”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tuesday lectures
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The lectures could be improved if recorded to offer reinforcement of material. It is quite hard to catch up with material if you had missed a class or if you had struggled fully understanding material during class.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Thursday examples
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>“I feel like the examples (on Thursdays) are much easier than the labs. I always understand the examples but am really confused on the labs. But besides that I haven&amp;rsquo;t found anything else an issue!”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I wish the Thursday lectures gave fewer hints and were a bit longer (maybe even more than finishable in class), but that&amp;rsquo;s a minor critique.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Too easy&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More instruction during Thursday lab would be great. Doing the lab on the board would be helpful.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Maybe explain a bit more about the code and terminology during Thursday labs, and go through the examples together&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Go through some examples together as a group with me coding rather than using scaffolded code on Thursdays (a couple people mentioned this)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I think last class' end 10-15minutes of spontaneous exercises for the whole class were fun where we had to figure out how to to simple tasks without the scaffolding. I think that&amp;rsquo;s a great way to push us students to code on our own and be problem solvers with R, and can be used in conjunction with the current class structure.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Least helpful: Readings. A couple people also said this about reflections.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I feel like the readings can be a bit much, some of the readings are incredibly long and then the same content is covered in lecture, so I feel disincentivized to do all the readings every week.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Office hours: a couple people said they would like me to hold office hours on Friday or Monday rather than Thursday&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Nathan Lesser: Despite the grand opening, the course has been awesome. I have many more compliments than critiques. I do wish the pace were a bit faster, possibly extending the Thursday examples and giving less guidance.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I really want to shift to working locally. I know that we can do that on our own, but I wish there is guidance on that.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I think I would learn a lot more if the labs just included the questions with none of the code pre-filled out. This is how AEM python and SQL were taught and while they were more difficult, I learned more quickly.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>See question 13. Other students have mentioned this desire to not have any &amp;ldquo;helper&amp;rdquo; code as well. Other than that, I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying the class!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Split of lectures/examples
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>one student:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>I&amp;rsquo;m not the biggest fan of 1.25 hours of just lecture on Tuesdays because its a coding class and the assignments are purely labs. (I don&amp;rsquo;t really count the reflections because they are very short and quick)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Just an idea maybe have the examples and lectures interwoven in both classes. The lecture could be split into two and we do the first half of the lecture and the first half of the examples on Tuesday. On Thursday, we&amp;rsquo;d do the second half of the lecture and second half of the examples.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>another student:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tuesday lectures are tough to process a lot of the information from the PowerPoint. I learn way more from Thursday than Tuesday.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I think something could change with the Tuesday Lecture format. I really don&amp;rsquo;t get much out of Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s lecture and would prefer just more workshops like on Thursday. Similar to when I took Reza Moghimi&amp;rsquo;s courses, I really liked how it was mostly working alongside him to get a feel of the material.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>[some other people argued the other way that the structure was good specifically because of this split, and many people just through the structure worked well in general]&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>One person said they liked me making up random questions at the end of class (when I needed to fill time)&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>